okay so you caught me in my magic moment
hey I'm Ali deser artist and filmmaker
but I'm here to speak to you about
Professor Joanna sopia who's just an
amazing raw food artist and a great
individual and what you see before me is
what's saving my life five days ago I
got a call from my doctor that my liver
uh enzymes were elevated too far my um
yeah I was ready to check out sis drop
dead somewhere and not be around for my
grandchildren great-grandchildren I
immedately called Professor Joanna and
I've been in this intensive now for 4
days folks it's amazing after 6 months
of not sleeping through the night an
amazing feeling uh to rest store like
that I'm just concerned about getting my
indic consist and those things I
mentioned in in order but I've lost 10
pounds so yeah yeah I still got a bit of
a dad bot but I'm feeling pretty Sprite
right now and that's because of these
beautiful smoothies raw organic fully
energized Foods we don't know how much
we have lost because we've gone so far
from nature we can't do this in the
supermarket we need to have the
knowledge and the best way for you to do
that excuse me can I try a green one the
kind of
savory I know she's got cilantro on this
one one of my favorite foods what you
can do is by you going and doing the
super happy body program as Joanna's
with a little s in there then ra foods
plural.com go there just give a look and
a read give yourself 15 minutes to maybe
cure your diabetes get out of that range
drop some weight that you wanted to drop
just feel better I was in 10year
depression mode all that's changed
because I made it my mind and reached
out for help no Johanna ra foods.com
it's just Johanna it's just I'm your
buddy I'm your friend I'm just Johanna
to you johanna's ra food okay
never ceases to amaze me